Guide to the Augustus Ward Loomis papers, 1803-1897
Loomis, Augustus Ward papers, 1803-1897
- Miscellaneous researchers' materials, 1950s-1970s (Folder 12)